Message me on WhatsApp. If you have a
claim and it gets rejected, you find out that
you have a serious illness and are
in the hospital, you apply for the lights off, the cost of that will be borne,
and the film gets
rejected. To avoid facing such situations,
it is important for one to know what are the
relationships that can lead to
your claim being rejected. Today we will
talk about toppers, because of which your
insurance claim gets rejected.
Before starting the video, I would like to introduce you to the
synonyms of life in Central and
Western Europe, associated with Clean Chit, so
that you can like it.
Because for us, whether
small or big, it is very common to take these foreign policies. If
Kabir ever
needs an emergency, then NCI will cover your
insurance claim. And if that is not there, then
come and see how
heartbreaking and haunting it can be. So
first of all, I would like to tell you that
no insurance company rejects this claim without reason.
If they do without
reason, then the insurance regulator
is very strict on them.  If IRDA comes, then friend, it is
answerable to IDBI, their song regulation,
if they are playing music, then
they also have to give further justification that
they should reset and the date is
from 500ml profile that we need to know those ground reasons, it is important to
know those major features due to
which we can reduce the chances of claim reaction
and because the competition is so high,
every investor would want their claim
settlement rate to be as solid as possible,
you will take their through insurance, the
biggest reason is this, I am telling you this today
from my accident, we get at
least six calls every day, at
least we get 7 to 10 in which you
people are asking for assistance for the cream,
you are not getting anything done at this time,
your response is not giving any information, you do
not know what is the status of the cream, cash has been
paid, so most of the time me and
my team spend a lot of time on it, the
time of ninety-five crops, this is that your
reaction to climate action is Visent
description, current times and disposal  You have
not shared proper material information
with the insurance company, which
policy you had taken, there can be many questions about it, like
you did
not have Avengers at that time, it is important to tell this, secondly
you did not know that this is material and
important information, thirdly you thought
that maybe this element is there or not, there can be
many such questions, so my
reaction here is that life transparency
in correct or incorrect information
insurance policy is a contract, it is
your principle of agreement, whatever
you are telling, the insurance company will accept whatever is
written in the application form
and on that basis the policy will be
started, if the insurance company finds out that
you had hidden something or you had
given some incomplete information, then there can be a clean reaction, so that is why you are
filling the application form, clean it properly, fill it
intelligently and do it from Karauli
and that is why the insurance company does
tele underwriting on it, that means the
application form which you have filled, that
underwriter  He goes to the insurance company and they check it
before the politician and some such things, so I will
call you and ask you again the information
that Malviya ji, yes some field is
missing and many times this happens, I can
tell you that it is not filled in the form
but on the call you people ask these medical
specific questions, they question you, they
ask you whether this was not there or that was not there, the
answer to some question or the other comes out to be additional, do
your best to listen to whatever
information you know, whatever you know about your
medical information, necessary information,
please tell that to the insurance company, do
not hide it because as I said the
objective of the insurance policy is not
only on the policies, it is that if
any cream comes tomorrow then the advection
probability will be killed tomorrow, so it should be decided
if you do not make the border work properly, if
it is set on the principles then the sample will
not be automatically done, I would
like to make a pause, what happens is that if you
port the policy then I want to do this
portability  I have made a video in which it is
also explained very early that you can refer,
so when you port the policy, at that
time you think that you have already informed the city, there is
no need to inform them, it is not like that,
underwriting is your duty,
so you should answer the questions of the new inch and the person you are going with, so
see, after the younger son, you will get
disappointment and you should not feel that you have made a
wrong decision, after supporting, then
tell your proper material information to the city of New York as well, like you
congratulated your old pride, you have to see improvement in your center, the
next reaction is the
villain of the team reaction, when the premium
payment is released, the company gives you a great
teacher, the company generally gives you a 30-day
rester that you will
not lose any of your benefits within the first day,
your continuity will not be lost, you should
renew your initial contract,
if you do not do it then the polish may
turn yellow and you will have to
start all over again, so the
real amount should not be included in your health insurance premium anywhere because man
Let me take
your exam dated 25th January 21 and I am
giving you a copy of the President's Information of the 30s for a month, but in this torn
country, if any cream comes, any
medical history, any dialogue happens, then it will create a
problem in it, if any claim comes, then even a
clean will not be given in it, then
you and it ends inside it, so do
not do grade three girl net, so that
in health insurance, if you have any
problem with the cream, then you get Great Leader
Life Insurance, that you can
do it without any lace with SIM after one month, after one month on premium, but her
line was a great spirit, according to me, it should
not be done and I would say this
because a lot of Ras Malai is coming across people that
right now the financial year is tight, but we will
not be able to pay, we will renew it after some time, do
not make such a mistake, if the account
is also tight and understand that if any claim
comes, from where will you get money from the pocket of Buddhahood,
then you will not renew these foreign policies,
so this teacher should consider it as an
action, health  Insurance
premium, this life insurance premium
is half the expense, which means we should consider it as
necessary like other household expenses, so if we pay for
food, clothing and shelter, then
food, clothing and shelter are
necessary, we cannot survive without it,
so its result
should also be kept separately, reduce it a little by a penny,
but
definitely share the insurance premium, the next reason for
reaction is that many people do not know about policy
building, policy benefits or
what is included in the policy, whether they are students, there are many
people who
go into the details, there are already
many people who do
not want to understand at all, according to Chinese zodiac, they have taken
health insurance, it is
Fuli's birthday tomorrow, he will take it, it is
not my responsibility to take insurance, it is not like that, there are a
lot of
tuitions in polythene, so for this I have
also made some videos that the policy has tea in it,
because of this there are lighting and collections in it, there was
no complaint, in health
insurance there are cuts and swellings and things, in
Amazon you will not get more than that, which
means in some cases it happens that after some time
2 years Singh Prabhat Khabar will be done but you will
not get it in the comments, so you
must refer to this, watch these videos and
definitely check your policy because the
policy can do dimple, that is
its recommendation, what is prominently
excluded is the meter which is not covered by the policy, so
if you know this then
you will not get an appointment for that,
like many times dental treatment of equal amount
but have always been there, the
policy was running for dental treatment, then you will feel
change with time, but I had taken a
policy and they are not giving me dental treatment news, if it is
not kabaddi then that is
why I will not get it, so please like, share and
it was fully aware that what is the murder,
what is the thing that you do not understand, the next question is
delay in filing of bus mint leaves, we give you
some time for your claim
and now we give you pimpl time,
how much time to file your insurance claim,
you do not side with it, so you
can visit all these,
you have full right, but if you give logical reasons
A proper entertainment gives this weight
that I could not decide it
Patnaik and Justice is important
why only by taking half first of all if you have to
file the information then there is no need to delete
and there is no need to give them another loan that
you have respect from the net what
I told you I found the fusion of
insurance which is Maithili contrast in this it happens that
if you try to harm yourself it is
called cell inflicting because of that a huge
claim comes
because of this someone's mother so insurance
companies who tried to if that event happened
yours is the biggest example from Ujjain
and you are
driving with alcohol or drugs while drinking right handwriting and it is
said that
suppose health insurance comes life
insurance accident happens
hospitalization will be updated and if life
insurance is worth then
information will not come out in that veins you should
try to harm yourself
you were Jain this note carefully are you not
taking  After seeing the reasonable and watching the film, if
you are not in such a situation then you will not
get it, but it will not happen, I
would like to say that insurance contrast 34 is a
lot, it is a principle on some of your
principles, Principal Pradeep, I
made a video, you can prefer it, the
link of which is in the description box, if these
principles are compromised somewhere, then if you do
not see the claim in front of you, then it
can reject the claim, then that principle is the biggest
important thing for you, as I
told you, Amos, good set, so keep your disclosure
proper, that is, do your best, whatever else has to happen,
you cannot change it
and finally now there is a regulator, which is the
insurance regulator IRDA, only and
complete information is shared with the policy holder,
what is the cancer
treatment, are shows and the entire make, their effort is to
work in favor of the policy holder, whatever they do, whatever
information will be of your city, whatever will be
told to you, your complaint will be heard, there is the Grievance
Department, now there is an IT man who will hear your complaint, you can file
your complaint if you get an idea  If the
result is Kumkum, then they
can definitely do it. So, this was my
video in which I told you
what could be the major reasons for killing reactions.
I would like to tell you that if you
keep these points in mind and still your
favorite is pass, as I mentioned,
you can talk to the insurance company in the grievances department.
You
can talk to the ombudsman or you
can also complain to IRDA. If you do
n't get help from here also, then this
company has Equal Insurance Samadhan, so you
can approach them and they will help you
in cancelling. If we
talk about Insurance Samadhan, then Equal Insurance
Samadhan is a company that helps you
in getting your loan money from the insurance company, so it is simple.
You can register for your claim through the link given below.
If you have any grievance and
you are not able to get it cleared, then
these people will help you. They have already
settled many claims.
You can check the stars among the people who have helped in the link below.  If
you go there, you will
find substance there. If you want to ask anything, you
can type our WhatsApp number with email
ID.
If you want to share your grievances with us,
we will reach out to you and resolve them and
promise to provide you a solution. And
a reminder, if you have not subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe to
my channel and Yashoda so that you keep
getting the circulation on time. Take care of yourself. Make Vikas
tasty. See you soon in the next video
with a new video. If you have made a big mistake, then
mix and you can comment. Kota is
over, my best in those days, let's
take off your pants, knowledge, so
I am running my race, medical expert, do it, it has happened
[music]
do it